Guide to the John D. Krumboltz Papers SC0219
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accessio ARCH-2016-137
  - Career Beliefs Inventory
    - CBI Scale Descriptions (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Minority career beliefs (Alford), 1989 Aug 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Cerritos Comm. College (Young), 1992 Jun 29 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - University of North Carolina librarian study (Bohanon), 1993 Jun 14 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - CBI site codes (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - MSU study: Carol Lunney, 1992 Oct 15 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Michigan Willow Run: Goodman, 1992 Jun 22 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Oakland University CBI study (splete), 1990 Apr 25 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Estimating satisfaction from CBI, 1990 Jun 8 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Boys Town CBI study (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - GLM ANOVA: student x sex, Moreau, 1990 Jan (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - GLM ANOVA: occupst x sex, Texas, 1990 Jan (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Manova: items 1-9 at Texas, 1990 Jan (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - CBI: ideas for revision, 1989 December (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Regression Analyses - CBI, 1990 May (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - University of Virginia: Spencer Niles, 1992 Oct 21 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - CBI in Indiana (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Penn state university CBI (Rayman) (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - James Lick H.S. CBI study, 1990 Oct 28 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Cognitive Restructuring Prevention
    - Stress reduction, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Reification in Legal Reasoning, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Rosenhan, D. L. on being sane in insane places, 1973 Jan 19 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Goldfried, Marvin R. D'Zurilla, T. J. a Behavioral-Analytic Model for Assessing Competence (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bandura, A. Psychological mechanisms of aggression (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Trexler, Larry D. Karst, Thomas O. Rational-Emotive Therapy, Placebo, and No-treatment effects on Public Speaking Anxiety (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Wolfe, Janet L. Short-term effects of modeling/behavior rehearsal, modeling/behavior rehearsal-plus-rational therapy, placebo, and no treatment on assertive behavior, 1975 Oct (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Pepinsky, H.B. a Metalanguage of Text (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Hosford, R.E. A review of observational learning counseling strategies: modeling self-observation and self-as-a-model (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Corno, L. Cognitive appraisals in academic motivation: a review with recommendations for teaching (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Bandura, A. Self-reinforcement: theoretical and methodological consideration (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Bandura, A. Self-efficacy: towards a unifying theory of behavioral change (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Bandura, A. the self and mechanisms of agency (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Bandura, A. Cervone, D. "Self-evaluative and self-efficacy mechanisms governing the motivational effects of goal systems (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Bandura, A., Reese, L. Adams, N. "Micro-analysis of Action and Fear Arousal as a Function of Different Levels of… (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Bandura, A. Schunk, D.H. Cultivating Competence, "Self-Efficacy and Intrinsic Interest through proximal self-motivation (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Bandura, A., Adams, N.E., Hardy, A.B., Howells, G.N. Tests of the Generality of Self-Efficacy Theory, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Danish, S.J., Smye, M.A. Nowak, C.A. Developmental Intervention, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Danish, S.J., Smyer, M.A. The unintended consequences of requiring a license to help (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Erickson/Horan/Hackett. Thinking and Feeling Bad, 1991 Aug 12 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Eysenck, H.J. "Human learning individual differences: the genetic dimension", 1993 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Phillips, D.C. Education from the Perspective of Philosophy of Science, 1978 Sep (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Phillips, D. Orton, R. "The New Causal principle of cognitive learning theory: perspectives on Bandura's…, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Kiesler, Charles A. A Motivational Theory of Stimulus Incongruity, with applications for such phenomena as dissonance and self-attribution (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Maultsby, Maxie C. Graham, D.T. Controlled study of effect psycho-therapyon self-reported maladaptive traits, anxiety scores and psychosomatic disease attitudes, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Burkhead, David Edward. The reduction of Negative Affect in Human Subjects: A Laboratory investigation of rational-emotive psychotherapy (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Carter, Dianne K. Feminist and Non-Sexist Psychotherapy (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Meichenbaum, Donald. Cognitive-behavior modification newsletter, 1976 Apr (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Meichenbaum/Cameron "Clin potential/pitfalls in Mad/SCPP (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Cog. Beh. Ther. Conf, 1976 Apr 3 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Rational-emotive therapy versus systematic desensitization in the treatment of stuttering, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Cognitive factors in sexual arousal: the role of distraction, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Meichenbaum, Donald H. Cognitive modification of test anxious college students (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Kanter, Norman Jay. A Comparison of Self-control Desensitization and Systemic Rational Restructuring for the Reduction of interpersonal anxiety, 1976 Jan (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Modifying Behavior outcome rules: a pilot study Curtis S. Wilbur (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Staats, Arthur W. Language behavior therapy: A derivative of social behaviorism (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Sociolinguistics and the counseling process Richard L. Conville/Allen E. Ivey, 1975 May (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Handout originals: Cog. Restruct. Workshop (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Div. 17 preconvention workshop cognitive restructuring in counseling, 1976 Sep (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Token reinforcement, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Skinner Freedom + Control of man, 1972 Mar (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Program for effective personal problem solving (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Prevention in Counseling (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Sprinthall, N.A. Moral and psychological development: a curriculum for secondary schools, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Prevention of counseling problems (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Denga, D.I. "Some characteristics of polygynous marriages in Nigeria and the role of the counsellor (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Multiculturalism, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Soliman, A.M. "the arab woman: socialization education, and work: implications for counselling, 1982 Sep 5-9 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Sexual equality in counseling (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Strong vocational interest blank Changes for 1972 by Dabid Campbell (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Vocational Exploratory behavior inventory, 1980 Aug (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - laFromboise+ Foster "Cross-cultural Training" (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - LINA legal matters (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Planned Happenstance book (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - New Happenstance Book (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Never make a CD", 2001 Jun (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Planned Happenstance references (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Permissions, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Evaluations, 2000 Nov 3 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Workshop on PH - Ottawa, 2001 Jan (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Titles and Headings, 2000 Mar (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Cartoons (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Stories, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Quotations, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Movie subtitles "Creating…" (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - PH Speech, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Happenstance: overhead slides (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Chap. 1 Don't make a decision PH (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - 2. Make the most (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Wake Up (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Try It, 2002 Sep (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Chap. 6 Try It -- You might like it PH (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - 5. Making Mistakes PH (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - 6. Create Lucky Breaks (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - 7. Accept, then Learn, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - 9. Retire, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Used (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - NO, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Workshop Presentations, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Receipts, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Ed. 237/Psych 252 Psychological Assessment, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Test Information for Ed. 237, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Ed. 237 Psych. Assess, 1989 Spring (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Ed. 237 handouts (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Test critique exercise, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Example of horrible questionnaire, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Test Construction Guide: ETS, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Accreditation Licensing
    - MOMM Cartel, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Palo Alto University (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - PGSP clinic (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Politics, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Post-doctoral internships, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Program planning and competency forms (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Psychology license, 1989 Jul (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Psychologist Job Search - Zimbardo materials, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Pupil personnel services standards, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Public relations (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Registration after Internship Agreement, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - School counseling program in California, 1990 Aug 13 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Sexual harrassment (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Standards for Providers of Psychological services, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Substance abuse course, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Advanced study center (Fellowship) National Center for Research in Vocational Education, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Personal, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Requests for Career selection theory, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Colony on the Moon, Norman Feingold Frank Womer, Gamblers, 1986 Aug 5 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Expenses - travel, 1977-1983 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Files in University Archives, 1969-1980 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Foreign visitors, 1966-1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Fundamental Standard and the Honor Code, 1963 Oct 8 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - J.D.K. expense reports, 1989 Aug 29 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Picture of JDK (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Ideas (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Crime: prevention + rehabilitation (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - logic problem on island murders (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Pictures - JDK, 1973 May 23 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - J.D. Krumboltz vita, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Biography of JDK, 2001 Mar 8 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Annual reports of professional activities, 1986-2002 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Sabbatical banking, 1989-2008 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - self-significance, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - University of Minnesota, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - APA accreditation self-study, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Accreditation, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Accreditation: raw material, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - APA accreditation self-study, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - APA accreditation, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - APA Accreditation, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - APA accreditation of PSE, 1985 May 10 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Annual accredation reports, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Accreditation procedures critera- APA, 1980 Oct (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - APA, 1985-1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Accreditation rule changes, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Accreditation, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Accreditation info files, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Application for accreditation counseling psychology program Stanford University, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - APIC association of psychology internship centers (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 Aug (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1993 Sep (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Cases (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Tolman's Learning Theory (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Hobbs: The Neo-New Psychology-Beer Motivation (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Evaluation check list for simulated teaching (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Problem on ordering bathing beauties (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Demonstrations in Educ. Psych, 1958 Nov 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Test on Zif and Boz (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Schizophenic letter, 1958 Sep 21 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Teaching concepts and skills in simulated teaching (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Insuring transfer and retention in simulated teaching, 1964 Jul (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Clifford, Margaret M. have we underestimated the facilitative effects of failure? (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Gage, N.L. "When does research on teaching yield implications for practice?", 1982 Oct 22 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Gagne, Robert M. The learning basis of teaching methods, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Snow. Aptitude-treatment interaction in psychotherapy (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Licensing and Credentialing in counseling psychology (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Educational and Professional Standards for Marriage and Family Counselors (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Laws relating to Marriage, Family, and Child Counselors and Licensed Educational Psychologists, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Licensure of Counselors, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Psychology examining committee, 1995-2000 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Psychology examining committee, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Division 17 Licensure, 1975-1978 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Professional practice of psychology legal, regulatory, and licensure issues, 1983 Jan (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - SCI, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - SCI intake forms (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Task force, SCI, 1990 Winter (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Stanford Counseling Institute, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - SCI Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Stanford Counseling Institute Policies, 1978-1982 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - SCI Policies and Procedures, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - SCI Policy Statements, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Stanford Institute for Behavioral Counseling, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Summer supervision for SCI counselors, 1981 Jun (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Stanford Counseling Institute Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - SCI, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Stanford Counseling Institute, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Stanford Counseling Institute Documents, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Stanford Counseling Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Annual report SIBC, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - S.I.B.C., 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Stanford Institute for Behavioral Counseling (SIBC), 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Stanford Institute for Behavioral Counseling, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Portion forms, 1987 Fall (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Winter, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - practicum record form, 1988 Spring (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Tests Measurements
    - Example of Well-written minutes, 1983 Feb (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Reliability of Essay grading, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Code of Fair testing practices in education (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Culture fair tests (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Performance Assessments (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - School testing videotape (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Multiple-choice items for a test of teacher competence in educational measurement (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Accuracy of self-ratings (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - California psychological inventory (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Salience inventory (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Values scale (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Bolles, Richard N. the Quick Job-Hunting Map (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Holland's self-directed research, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Delphi Method (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Racial Test Bias 1. T.A. Cleary, Science, 1972, 176, 113-114. 2. Gage, Shockley, Jensen Page, Phi Delta Kappan, 1972, 5 articles (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Experimental Designs - Campbell + Stanley (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Poor scholar's soliloguy (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - The Voice of the low IQ (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Alternative grading systems (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Ladle rat rotten hut (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Problems in test interpretation set B (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Problems in testing- stencils (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - directions for preparing an achievement test (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Barron-Welsh art scale (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Knapp, R. R./Knapp, L. COPS systems (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Problem solving inventory, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Dunnette, M. D. psychometric theory in handbook of industrial and organizational psychology (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Maudsley Personality Inventory by H.J. Eysenck (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Attention Deficit Disorders Evaluation Scale (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Computer test interpretation, 1991 Aug 9 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Group Embedded Figures Test (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Popham, W. James. Whats wrong with standardized achievement tests? (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Career I.D. job activity checklist (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Campbell interest and skill survey, 1992 Aug (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Career attitudes and strategies inventory- Holland (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Career factors inventory (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Career thoughts inventory (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Enneagram (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Firo-B (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Hypnosis susceptibility (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Interpersonal Locus of Control Scale (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Job search knowledge scale (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Kefauver-Hand Guidance Tests, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Kuder (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - My vocational situation (Holland) (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Attention Deficit Disorders Evaluation Scale (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Hopkin's image recognition test (UFO) (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Life values invention (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Myers-Briggs tyep indicator- form F (continued) (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - MINI diagnostic interview, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Multiple intelligences (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Personal concerns inventory (PCI) (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Strong interest inventory (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Strong college major report (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Self-directed search (professional manual) (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Kudor form DD (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Stanley, Julian C. predicting college success of the educationally disadvantaged (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Testing for minimal competency (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - The SAT score decline: a summary of related research Hunter M. Breland, 1976 Jan (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Zajone, R.B. intellectual environment and intelligence, 1975 Oct (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Cronbach, L. J. Designing Educational Evaluations (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Minnesota mental paroxysm index (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - A measure of vocational maturity Bert W. Westbrook and Joseph W. Parry- Hill, Jr. (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Career development test items to assess specific instructional objectives in the cognitive domain Westbrook, Bert W. (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Value search, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Ford/Nichols. The Assessment of Personal Goals (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - My vocational situation (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Decision making questionnaire (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Career development inventory Donald E. Super and David J. Forrest, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Minnesota job career values -- description questionnaire (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - SCL - 90 - R symptom checklist (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Holland, Self- directed career program, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Harren, V.A. assessment of career decision-making (form B) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Nichols: tracing your values (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - 16 PF1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Super, D.E./Nevill, D.D. The Values Scale (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Thoresen, C. Coping with Tests: A Manual (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - CMAS career mastery inventory (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Krumboltz, Sheppard, Jones, Johnson, Baker, Vocational Problem-solving experiences for stimulating career exploration and interest, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Krumboltz, Sheppard, Jones, Johnson + Baker. Abstract of final report vocational problem solving experiences for simulating career exploration interest, USOE, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Krumboltz, JD, Varenhorst, B. B. "nonverbal factors in the effectiveness of models in counseling, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Thoresen, C. E., Krumboltz, J.D., Varenhorst, B. B., "Sex of Counselors and Models: Effect on Client Career Exploration", 1967 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. "Behavioral Counseling and Human Decision Making", 1968 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Abstract AERJ, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Krumboltz, J. D., Factors Affecting the Design of Effective Teaching Machine Programs, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Krumboltz, J. D., "A behavioral Approach to group counseling and therapy", 1968 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Future Directions for Counseling Research, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Thoresen C.E Krumboltz, J.D., "Similarity of Models and Clients in Behavioral Counseling: Two Experimental Studies", 1968 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Krumboltz, Baker and Johnson Vocational Problem-solving experiences for stimulating career exploration and interest: Phase II, Hew, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. "Behavioral Counseling in Groups", 1969 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Bergland, B. W. Krumboltz, J. D. "An Optimal Grade Level for Career Explorations", 1969 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Abstract -- Vocational Problem-solving Esperiences for Stimulating Career Exploration and Interest: Phase II (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Krumboltz, J. D., Bergland, B.W. "Experiencing Work Almost Like it is", 1969 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Hamilton, J. A., Krumboltz, J. D. "Simulated Work Experience: How realistic sgould it be?", 1969 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Jones, G. B., Krumboltz, J. D. "Stimulating Vocational Exploration through Film-mediated problems.", 1970 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. "Counseling and the New Morality", 1970 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Krumboltz, J.D., "Job Experience Kits", 1970 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - UNICK "Reducing Sexual Desire", 1970 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Krumboltz, J. D., Review of Robert H. Woody, Behavioral Problem Children in the Schools: Recognition, Diagnosis and Behavioral Modification, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Nelson, D.E. Krumboltz, J.D. "Encouraging Career Exploration through 'Simulated Work' and Vocational Detective Experiences.", 1970 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Thoresen, C.E., Hosford, R.E., "Determining Effective Models for Counseling Clients of Varying Competencies", 1970 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Behavioral Systems training program for counselors, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. Page, E. N. "How the Behavioral Approach can Help a Beleaguered Counselor" in Notre Dame Journal of Education, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. Menefee, M. "The Changed Behavior of Behavior Changers by 1984" Canadian Counsellor, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. Krumboltz, H. B. Changing Children's Behavior. Prentice-Hall, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. Baker, R. D. Vocational Guidance for the 1970s Henry Borow "Behavioral Counseling for Vocational Decisions, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Happenstance Learning theory, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Practical Career Counseling Applications of the Happenstance Learning Theory, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Veterans creating a New Life, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Krumboltz, J. D. and McHargue, R. M. "There is Nothing Beyond Freedom and Dignity" Counseling and Values, Wtr, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Johnson, Baker, Krumboltz "Generating Interests through Vocational Simulation Experience" the Journal of Counseling Psychology (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - "Rationale for a Competency-Based Program in Counseling" draft J. D. Krumboltz, C. E. Thoresen, and S. M. Zifferblatt, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 47)